http://www.millersmerrymanor.com/privacy-policy

Visitation Restrictions Due to COVID-19:All Miller’s buildings are currently offering scheduled outdoor and indoor visitation In accordance with the directive issued by CDC, IDH and our governmental authorities.
Certain facility, community, and/or weather conditions may temporarily limit visitation. Please contact the facility to determine specific hours, schedules, and current county conditions, along with any further existing guidelines.
For more information, please click here.
Proud to be 100% Employee Owned!
Healthcare Professionals
Contact Us
Schedule a Tour
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Miller's Health Systems collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the MillersMerryManor.com website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Miller's Merry Manor/Miller's Health Systems.Personal identification informationWe may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, subscribe to the newsletter, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.Non-personal identification informationWe may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.Web browser cookiesOur Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.How we use collected informationMiller's Health Systems may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:To improve customer service
Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.To personalize user experience
We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.To improve our Site
We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.To send periodic emails
We may use the email address to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.How we protect your informationWe adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.Sharing your personal informationWe do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.Third party websitesUsers may find content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.Changes to this privacy policyMiller's Health Systems has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.
Your acceptance of these termsBy using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.Contacting usIf you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:
Miller's Health Systems
PO Box 4377
Warsaw, IN 46581
574-267-7211
This document was last updated on March 19, 2014.
Interested in touring a location or need more information? Contact us.
